翻译，特效，压制: 布尔
字体: 思源宋体 SemiBold
思源黑体 Regular
Deep In The hundred acred wood
在百亩森林的深处
Where Christopher Robin plays
克里斯托弗·罗宾在那里玩耍
Plays everyday
每天都在玩
You'll find the enchanted neighborhood
你会找到拥有魔法的邻居
Of Christopher's childhood days
陪伴着克里斯托弗·罗宾的童年
A donkey named Eeyore is his friend
一个叫屹耳的小驴是他的朋友
学习音轨在简介中的原简介赞助页面中
There's Kanga and little Roo
还有袋鼠妈妈和小豆
Oh and Tigger, too
对还有跳跳虎
There's Rabbit and Piglet
瑞比和小猪
And there's Owl
以及猫头鹰
But most of all Winne The Pooh
但最好的朋友还是小熊维尼
Oh Winnie The Pooh
哦 小熊维尼
Winnie The Pooh
小熊维尼
chubby little cubby all stuffed with fluff
它是全身毛茸茸的可爱小熊
He's Winnie The Pooh
他就是小熊维尼
Winnie The Pooh
小熊维尼
Willy nilly silly old bear
也是犹豫不决的大笨熊
Where's our good friend
我们的好朋友去那儿了
Winnie The Pooh
小熊维尼
chubby little cubby all stuffed with fluff
它是全身毛茸茸的可爱小熊
He's Winnie The Pooh
他就是小熊维尼
Winnie The Pooh
小熊维尼
Willy nilly silly old soft and round and hard and cold
也是犹豫不决 又圆又软又冷酷的大笨熊
No honey to spend
没有蜂蜜去花费了
He's our bear
他是我们的熊